A good morning all five of you, first of all
focus on the results that are coming today.
From the second space, you will see Federal Bank going sour.
Friends, Havells and
HDFC AMC, their numbers will also go up here. Let me
tell you about the bottom lines. There is a
long list which includes popular wedding
planning software and technology services,
governance technology, Jin-Jin International,
Sterlite, Hindustan Zinc, which will
earn you results. Son,
you must have kept an eye on its results as well. Apart from this, the
post-mortem numbers came in, in which the district's
shallow remaining numbers were visible and better than
estimate numbers are here. You will see that the
employment premium has increased by about nine
percent to Rs 4034 crore. Friends,
if you look at the company's profit, it has increased
from Rs 294 crore to Rs 313 crore.
Idea's IPO update is on the second
day of the issue. So far, this behavior has been seen 1.2 times. The
notification from retail investors has been
good and it is seen filling up two and a quarter times.
Now, where else can you invest money today?
Apart from this,
keep an eye on Garden Reach Shipbuilders here.  Because the
government will be seen doing a road show from today till tomorrow. There will be a
ban through video conferencing. The government has a
plan to sell 10% stake in it through its office.
I would like to bring something for you on Tata Communications of India,
where
bids have been invited for appointing bank accountants for the office
and the government will now send its entire
share, the remaining appendix percent, through it.
Now see, by
selling this share, the
government can raise around ₹10,000 (₹400). This saliva
vibrations will come out while writing and the
flavor of Tata Communications. The
target of completion by March 20 seems to be fixed at the moment. The
opening day of Vedanta is seen to be
coming on February 4. For Vedanta,
or people will see the news, the open offer special is seen
coming, which will be available on March 1st and will remain
open till March 15th and this will be available as soon as the
process is completed. The
price of the open offer was fixed at Rs. 10.60 per
share.  Holi Patan was celebrated peacefully.
Look here, the fans have
removed their stake in Vedanta. It has been
reduced from 70% to 16%. The
share of mutual funds has also
reduced to about five and a half percent in the last one week. There is
enthusiasm seen crying.
Narendra Chanchal Pal is buying. He used to hold 2% stake
but now his stake is
seen falling below one percent. Shivbuilding has also started on Federal Bank
and updates are coming. Show that.
Rakesh Jhunjhunwala has given his stake in the bank.
He used to hold 2.7% in this quarter.
He has reduced it to 2.4%.
When did its share in FD decrease this time? It
decreased from 2014 to 21.72% and the
share of mutual funds is big. It has
increased by five percent to 19%. After reading this, it is shown to be increasing to 50%.
Keep an eye on Indian Bank. The
company's board meeting will be held on January 22. Happy Happy. A
decision will be taken here on raising capital through rights issue.  As
consumer news comes, the
company has announced to buy maturity stake in Big Basket,
about two to two hundred and fifty
million dollars and plans to invest are
seen closed here and also in pharma,
plans to buy stake in 1mg are seen being made at the moment, so
cover for a news timer,
ok, then fill the full advance from you in Akshay,
first of all ICICI Lombard,
after the results, brokerage house,
if you see, this motor and pipes cigarettes
cream was very good but
increase in expenses, its brain cancer, you
see, through buying, while keeping the rent
intact, they have reduced the target,
removed 1850 to 1780, it is around 1515,
tomorrow's closing is around the same, if you see CLSA,
they have increased the target price
but have downgraded the rating, now by
changing the path of buying, give outperform
rating, target has been increased from 1615 to
around 1700,
take the opinion of JP Morgan Neutral, the target is around
half, they have
given a target of around 1360, apart from this, if you see
L&T Infotech here But the results
were good but the surprising thing is that
no brokerage house has
given a price above the current price. Tomorrow
's closing is around 4094. Macquarie has
maintained the outperform rating.
Morgan Stanley has given a buy rating of Rs 37 for the railing of the overbridge at
Rs 3450. Apart from this, the
last report on Tata Steel for now,
here Tata Metaliks and Tata Steel
BSNL are not good.
After this, the thumbs up of the brokerage house came, buy by
pressing here and
maintain the price. Tomorrow's closing is around the lower part of 850.
Morgan Stanley has maintained its rating
at 6840. Quarry has collected 815. Okay, so
this is you.